American Painting Section of the Mounted Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- C (Box 23–24)
  - Individual Artists (Box 25–26)
    - Copley, John Singleton, 1738-1815., total of 209 photographs. (Box 31)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: N-S, 14 (Box 32)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: T-W, 17 (Box 32)
      - Boston, 41 (Box 32)
      - Cambridge, 17 (Box 33)
      - London, 6 (Box 33)
      - New Haven, 11 (Box 33)
      - New York, 18 (Box 33)
      - Washington D.C., 13 (Box 33)
    - Corbino, Jon, 1905-., 4 (Box 33)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 1903-1972., 3 (Box 33)
    - Costigan, John E., 1888-1972., 5 (Box 34)
    - Covert, John, 1882-1960., 9 (Box 34)
    - Cox, Kenyon, 1856-1919., 7 (Box 34)
    - Cropsey, Jasper Francis, 1823-1900., 21 (Box 34)
    - Curry, John Stewart, 1897-1946., 21 (Box 34)
- D (Box 35)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "D" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Dai-Dau., 11 (Box 35)
    - Daingerfield, Elliot, 1859-1932., 3 (Box 35)
    - Darby, Henry F., act. 1853-1859., 1 (Box 35)
    - D'Arcangelo, Allan, 1933-., 2 (Box 35)
    - Darley, Felix, 1822-1888., 1 (Box 35)
    - Daugherty, James Henry, 1886-?., 4 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Dav., 10 (Box 35)
    - Davie, Alan, 1920-?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Davies, Kenneth, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Davis, Alexander Jackson, 1803-1898., 3 (Box 35)
    - Davis, James S., 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Davis, Joseph, 1832-1837., 3 (Box 35)
    - Davis, Ron, 1937-., 1 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Dea-Dek., 8 (Box 35)
    - De Camp, Joseph R., 1858-1923., 2 (Box 35)
    - Dechar, Peter, 1944-., 1 (Box 35)
    - Decker, Joseph, 1853-1924., 4 (Box 35)
    - Dee, Leo, 1931-., 1 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Del-Di., 19 (Box 35)
    - Delandy, Abraham, 1742-1795., 1 (Box 35)
    - De Niro, Robert, 1922-?., 3 (Box 35)
    - Denis, Agnes, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dessar, Louis Paul, 1867-?, 2 (Box 35)
    - Detwiller, Frederick K., 1882-1953., 4 (Box 35)
    - Dewing, Maria Oakey, 1855-1927., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dill, Laddie John, 20th c., 2 (Box 35)
    - Dinnerstein, Simon, 1943-., 3 (Box 35)
    - Dix, Harry, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dixon, Maynard, 1875-1946., 1 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Do-Dr., 18 (Box 35)
    - Dodd, Lamar, 1909-?., 2 (Box 35)
    - Dodd, Lois, 20th c., 3 (Box 35)
    - Dogancay, Burhan, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dolnick, Judith, 20th c., 2 (Box 35)
    - Donati, Erico, 1909-?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dougherty, Paul, 1877-?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Douglas, Lucy, act. 1820., 1 (Box 35)
    - Draper, William Franklin, 1912-?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dreier, Dorothea A., 1870-1923., 3 (Box 35)
    - Drexler, Rosalyn, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Drexler, Sherman, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Driggs, Elsie, 1883-1935., 1 (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Du., 16 (Box 35)
    - Du Bois, Yvonne, 20th c., 2 (Box 35)
    - Dubreuil, Victor, 20th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dudley, Robert, 19th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Duesberry, Joellyn, 1944-., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dugmore, Edward, 1915-?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Duncan, Frank, 1916-?., 2 (Box 35)
    - Durfee, Hazard, 1916-?., 2 (Box 35)
    - Du Smitiere, Pierre, 19th c?., 1 (Box 35)
    - Duyckinck, Evert, 17th c., 1 (Box 35)
    - Duyckinck, Gerret, 1660-1710., 2 (Box 35)
    - Dworkowitz, Alan, 1946-., 1 (Box 35)
    - Dzubas, Friedel, 1915-?., 1 (Box 35)
  - Individual Artists (Box 35–36)
    - Daphnis, Nassos, 1914-., 8 (Box 36)
    - Dasburg, Andrew, 1887-1979., 5 (Box 36)
    - Davey, Randall, 1887-1964., 3 (Box 36)
    - Davies, Arthur B., 1862-1928., total of 34 photographs. (Box 36)
      - Drawings, 4 (Box 36)
      - Location Unknown, 9 (Box 36)
      - Private Collection, 4 (Box 36)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 17 (Box 36)
    - Davis, Gene, 1920-1985., 8 (Box 36)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1901-., 5 (Box 36)
    - Davis, Stuart, 1894-1964., total of 45 photographs. (Box 36–37)
      - Private Collection, 20 (Box 37)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 10 (Box 37)
      - New York, 15 (Box 37)
    - Dearth, Henry Golden, 1864-1918., 7 (Box 37)
    - Deas, Charles, 1818-1867., 6 (Box 37)
    - Dehn, Adolf A., 1895-1968., 5 (Box 37)
    - De Kooning, Elaine, 1920-1989., 6 (Box 37)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1904-1997., total of 93 photographs. (Box 37–38)
      - Undated, 1 (Box 38)
      - 1938-1939, 3 (Box 38)
      - 1940-1949, 15 (Box 38)
      - 1950-1954, 5 (Box 38)
      - 1950-1954 cont., 23 (Box 38)
      - 1955-1959, 6 (Box 38)
      - 1955-1959, 11 (Box 38)
      - 1960-1969, 13 (Box 38)
      - 1970-1979, 10 (Box 38)
      - 1980-1982, 6 (Box 38)
    - Demuth, Charles, 1883-1935., total of 41 photographs. (Box 38–39)
      - Location Unknown, 14 (Box 39)
      - Private Collection, 3 (Box 39)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 13 (Box 39)
      - New York, 11 (Box 39)
    - Dewing, Thomas Wilmer, 1851-1938., 14 (Box 39)
    - Dickenson, Edwin Walter, 1891-1978., 9 (Box 39)
    - Dickinson, Preston, 1891-1930., 6 (Box 40)
    - Diebenkorn, Richard, 1922-1993., 22 (Box 40)
    - Diller, Burgoyne, 1906-1965., 7 (Box 40)
    - Dine, Jim, 1935-., 28 (Box 40)
    - Doughty, Thomas, 1793-1856., 14 (Box 40)
    - Douglas, Aaron, 1899-1979., 6 (Box 41)
    - Dove, Arthur G., 1880-1946., 21 (Box 41)
    - Dreier, Katherine S., 1887-1952., 6 (Box 41)
    - DuBois, Guy Pene, 1884-1958., 10 (Box 41)
    - Dunlap, William, 1766-1839., 10 (Box 41)
    - Durand, Asher B., 1796-1886., 36 (Box 41–42)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 12 (Box 42)
      - Individual Cities: New Haven, 8 (Box 42)
      - Individual Cities: New York, 16 (Box 42)
    - Durand, Frederick Frank, c.1800- c.1899., 4 (Box 42)
    - Durand, John, act. 1766-1782., 3 (Box 42)
    - Durrie, George Henry, 1820-1863., 6 (Box 42)
    - Duveneck, Frank, 1848-1919., 28 (Box 42–43)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 16 (Box 43)
      - Individual Cities: Cincinnati, 12 (Box 43)
    - Duyckinck, Gerardus, 1695-1746., 2 (Box 43)
- E (Box 43)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "E" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ea-Ev., 30 (Box 43)
    - Earl, James., 2 (Box 43)
    - Earl, Ralph E.W., 2 (Box 43)
    - Eastman, W.S., 2 (Box 43)
    - Eaton, J.N., 1 (Box 43)
    - Eaton, Wyatt., 1 (Box 43)
    - Eddy, Don., 1 (Box 43)
    - Eddy, Oliver T., 1 (Box 43)
    - Edmonds, William., 1 (Box 43)
    - Edmondson, William J., 1 (Box 43)
    - Elliott, Charles L., 3 (Box 43)
    - Emmet, Lydia Field., 1 (Box 43)
    - Emmons, Nathaniel., 1 (Box 43)
    - Emory, Ella., 2 (Box 43)
    - Erlebacher, Martha Mayer., 1 (Box 43)
    - Ernst, Jimmy., 3 (Box 43)
    - Eschner-Camp, Robin., 1 (Box 43)
    - Etting, Emlen., 1 (Box 43)
    - Evans, de Scott., 1 (Box 43)
    - Evans, J.G., 1 (Box 43)
    - Everett, Ann., 1 (Box 43)
    - Everett, Bruce., 1 (Box 43)
  - Individual Artists (Box 44)
    - Eakins, Thomas, 1844-1916., 287 (Box 44)
      - Drawings, 9 (Box 44)
      - Location Unknown, 7 (Box 44)
      - Private Collection, 4 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-B, 12 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: C-D, 17 (Box 44)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: F-Z, 19 (Box 44)
      - Individual Cities: New Haven, 24 (Box 44)
      - Individual Cities: New York, 17 (Box 45)
        - Individual Repositories: Metropolitan Museum Of Art, 15 (Box 45)
      - Individual Cities: Philadelphia, 11 (Box 45)
        - Individual Repositories: Jefferson Medical College, 11 (Box 45)
        - Individual Repositories: Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Art, 8 (Box 45)
        - Individual Repositories: Philadelphia Museum of Art, 7 (Box 45)
        - Individual Repositories: Philadelphia Museum of Art, cont., 38 (Box 45–46)
          - Oil Sketches/Studies, 19 (Box 46)
          - Portraits, Female, 21 (Box 46)
          - Portraits, Male, 15 (Box 46)
      - Individual Cities: Washington D.C., 11 (Box 46)
        - Individual Repositories: Joseph H. Hirshhorn Museum, 22 (Box 46)
    - Earl, Ralph, 1751-1801., 32 (Box 46–47)
      - Location Unknown, 1 (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-L, 13 (Box 47)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: M-Z, 7 (Box 47)
      - Individual Cities: New Haven, 11 (Box 47)
    - Eastman, Seth, 1808-1875., 9 (Box 47)
    - Ehninger, John Whetton, 1827-1889., 3 (Box 47)
    - Eichholtz, Jacob, 1776-1842., 6 (Box 47)
    - Eilshemius, Louis Michel, 1864-1941., 23 (Box 48)
    - Elmer, Edwin Romanzo, 1850-1923., 4 (Box 48)
    - Estes, Richard, 1932-., 9 (Box 48)
    - Etnier, Stephen, 1903-., 3 (Box 48)
    - Evergood, Philip, 1901-1973., 7 (Box 48)
- F (Box 49)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "F" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Fa-Fi., 14 (Box 49)
    - Farnsworth, Jerry., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fausett, Dean., 2 (Box 49)
    - Fawcett, John., 1 (Box 49)
    - Feininger, Theo., 3 (Box 49)
    - Ferrill, M.E., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fine, Perle., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fini, Leonor., 1 (Box 49)
    - Finster, Howard., 2 (Box 49)
    - Fiske, Gertrude., 1 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Fl., 13 (Box 49)
    - Flack, Audrey., 3 (Box 49)
    - Flagg, George W., 1 (Box 49)
    - Flagg, Jared B., 1 (Box 49)
    - Flannagan, John B., 2 (Box 49)
    - Flint, Alice Morland., 1 (Box 49)
    - Florsheim, Richard., 2 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Fo., 15 (Box 49)
    - Ford, Lauren., 2 (Box 49)
    - Forman, Alice., 1 (Box 49)
    - Forsberg, Patricia., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fortune, Euphemia Carlton., 2 (Box 49)
    - Fosburgh, James., 2 (Box 49)
    - Foster, Benjamin., 1 (Box 49)
    - Foster, John., 2 (Box 49)
    - Fournier, Alexis Jean., 2 (Box 49)
    - Fox, C.J., 1 (Box 49)
    - Foy, William., 1 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Fr-Fu., 20 (Box 49)
    - Francis, John F., 2 (Box 49)
    - Frank, Mary., 2 (Box 49)
    - Freckelton, Sondra., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fredenthal, David., 2 (Box 49)
    - Freeman, ?., 1 (Box 49)
    - French, Jared., 1 (Box 49)
    - Friend,Patricia., 1 (Box 49)
    - Fromkes, Maurice., 2 (Box 49)
    - Frost, Arthur B., 5 (Box 49)
    - Furnass, John Mason., 1 (Box 49)
  - Individual Artists (Box 50)
    - Faulkner, Barry, 1881-., 4 (Box 50)
    - Feininger, Lyonel, 1871-1956., 47 (Box 50)
      - Undated, 12 (Box 50)
      - - 1920's, 21 (Box 50)
      - 1930's -, 14 (Box 50)
    - Feke, Robert, 1707-1752., 47 (Box 50–51)
      - Location Unknown, 2 (Box 51)
      - Private Collection, 9 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-B, 9 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: C-L, 9 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: M-N, 8 (Box 51)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: P-Z, 10 (Box 51)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1906-., 4 (Box 52)
    - Ferren, John, 1905-1970., 6 (Box 52)
    - Fiene, Ernest, 1894-1966., 8 (Box 52)
    - Field, Erastus Salisbury, 1805- 1900., 13 (Box 52)
    - Fish, Janet, 1938-., 6 (Box 52)
    - Fisher, Alvan, 1792-1863., 4 (Box 52)
    - Francis, Sam, 1923-1994., 29 (Box 52)
    - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1928-., 35 (Box 53)
    - Freake Limner, act. 1670-1674., 11 (Box 53)
    - Freilicher, Jane, 1924-., 7 (Box 53)
    - Frieseke, Frederick Carl, 1874- 1939., 14 (Box 53)
    - Fuller, George, 1822-1884., 12 (Box 54)
- G (Box 54)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "G" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ga., 12 (Box 54)
    - Gablik, Suzi., 1 (Box 54)
    - Galkootz., 1 (Box 54)
    - Garber, Daniel., 3 (Box 54)
    - Garet, Jedd., 1 (Box 54)
    - Garrigan, Kim., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gauley, Robert David., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gay, Winkworth Allan., 4 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ge-Gl., 18 (Box 54)
    - George, Thomas., 2 (Box 54)
    - George, Vesper L., 1 (Box 54)
    - Georges, Paul., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gibbs Limner., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gibson, Charles., 1 (Box 54)
    - Giess, Alfred., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gifford, G.H., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gignoux, Regis., 2 (Box 54)
    - Gilbert, Charles Allan., 2 (Box 54)
    - Gilchrist, W.W., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gillespie, Frances Cohen., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gillespie, Gregory., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gilman, James Franklin., 1 (Box 54)
    - Glarner, Fritz., 2 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Go., 17 (Box 54)
    - Godwin, Judith., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goff, Lloyd Lozes., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goings, Ralph., 4 (Box 54)
    - Goldin, Leon., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goldring, Milton., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goldsmith, A., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goldthwaite, Anne., 2 (Box 54)
    - Gonzales, Julio., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goodes, Edward., 1 (Box 54)
    - Goodwin, Arthur Clifton., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gordon, Leon., 2 (Box 54)
    - Gornick, April., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gould, Walter G., 1 (Box 54)
    - Gouy, M.A., 1 (Box 54)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Gr., 11 (Box 55)
    - Grabach, John R., 1 (Box 55)
    - Granahan, David., 1 (Box 55)
    - Grant, J., 1 (Box 55)
    - Grausman, Philip., 1 (Box 55)
    - Gray, Henry P., 1 (Box 55)
    - Green, Samuel., 1 (Box 55)
    - Greenleaf, Benjamin., 3 (Box 55)
    - Groombridge, William., 1 (Box 55)
    - Gross, Chaim., 1 (Box 55)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Gu., 9 (Box 55)
    - Guerin, John., 1 (Box 55)
    - Gullager, Christian., 1 (Box 55)
    - Gussow, Alan., 1 (Box 55)
    - Guy, Seymour Joseph., 3 (Box 55)
    - Guyol de Guiran, Francois., 1 (Box 55)
  - Individual Artists (Box 55)
    - Gallatin, Albert E., 1881-1952., 6 (Box 55)
    - Ganso, Emil, 1895-1941., 5 (Box 55)
    - Gatch, Lee, 1902-1968., 5 (Box 55)
    - Gaulois, Paul, 1901-1943., 14 (Box 55)
    - Gay, Walter, 1856-1937., 13 (Box 55)
    - Gifford, Sanford Robinson, 1823- 1880., 13 (Box 55)
    - Glackens, William, 1870-1938., 25 (Box 55)
    - Golub, Leon Albert, 1922-., 6 (Box 56)
    - Goodnough, Robert Arthur, 1917-., 7 (Box 56)
    - Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1948., 42 (Box 56)
    - Gottlieb, Adolph, 1903-1974., 20 (Box 57)
    - Gottlieb, Adolph, cont. 1903-1974., 17 (Box 57)
    - Graham, John D., 1881-1961., 6 (Box 57)
    - Graves, Morris, 1910-., 20 (Box 57)
    - Graves, Nancy, 1940-1995., 3 (Box 57)
    - Gray, Cleve, 1918-., 6 (Box 58)
    - Greene, Balcomb, 1904-., 3 (Box 58)
    - Greene, Stephen, 1918-., 10 (Box 58)
    - Greenwood, John, 1727-1792., 15 (Box 58)
    - Grooms, Red, 1937-., 1 (Box 58)
    - Gropper, William, 1897-1977., 10 (Box 58)
    - Guglielmi, O. (Osvaldo) Louis, 1906-1956., 4 (Box 58)
    - Gundelfinger, John, 1937-., 8 (Box 58–59)
    - Guston, Phillip, 1913-1980., 42 (Box 59)
      - Undated, 6 (Box 59)
      - 1930-1949, 3 (Box 59)
      - 1950-1959, 15 (Box 59)
      - 1960-1979, 18 (Box 59)
    - Gute, Herbert Jacob, 1908-., 5 (Box 59)
    - Guy, Francis, 1760-1820., 4 (Box 59)
    - Gwathmey, Robert, 1903-., 3 (Box 59)
- H (Box 59–60)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "H" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Haa-Hap., 16 (Box 60)
    - Hafftka, Michael., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hafif, Marcia., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hagin, Nancy., 1 (Box 60)
    - Halaby, Samia., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hale, Philip Leslie., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hall, George Henry., 1 (Box 60)
    - Halpert, Samuel., 3 (Box 60)
    - Hamilton, James., 3 (Box 60)
    - Hammer, John J., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hansegger, J.K., 1 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Har-Haz., 21 (Box 60)
    - Hardy, Jeremiah Pearson., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hart, George Overbury., 3 (Box 60)
    - Hartigan, Grace., 4 (Box 60)
    - Hartwick, Hermann., 1 (Box 60)
    - Harvey, George., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hauer, Erwin., 1 (Box 60)
    - Havard, James., 1 (Box 60)
    - Havell, Robert the Younger., 2 (Box 60)
    - Haverle, John., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hayden, Palmer., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hayes, George A., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hazard, Barbara, 1 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: He-Hi., 22 (Box 60)
    - Headley, Joseph H., 1 (Box 60)
    - Helander, Bruce., 1 (Box 60)
    - Held, John Jr., 4 (Box 60)
    - Heming, Arthur., 3 (Box 60)
    - Hennings, Ernest Martin., 1 (Box 60)
    - Herzog, Herman., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hetzel, George., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hicks, Thomas., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hickson, Richard., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hill, John William., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hinchman, Margaretha., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hirsch, Stefan., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hirsh, C. Mortimer., 1 (Box 60)
    - Hirshfield, Morris., 1 (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Hu., 8 (Box 60)
    - Hubard, William J., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hull, Marie., 2 (Box 60)
    - Hultberg, John., 2 (Box 60)
    - Humphrey, Ralph., 2 (Box 60)
  - Individual Artists (Box 61)
    - Haas, Richard, 1936-., 6 (Box 61)
    - Haberle, John, 1856-1933., 13 (Box 61)
    - Harding, Chester, 1792-1866., 11 (Box 61)
    - Haring, Keith, 1958-1990., 7 (Box 61)
    - Harnett, William, 1848-1892., 43 (Box 61)
      - Location Unknown, 4 (Box 61)
      - Private Collection, 2 (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-D, 10 (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: E-O, 11 (Box 61)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: P-Z, 16 (Box 61)
    - Hart, James McDougal, 1828-1901., 3 (Box 62)
    - Hart, William M., 1823-1894., 6 (Box 62)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1877-1943., 56 (Box 62)
      - Location Unknown, 4 (Box 62)
      - Private Collection, 6 (Box 62)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 21 (Box 62)
      - Individual Cities: New York, 12 (Box 62)
      - Individual Cities: Philadelphia, 13 (Box 62)
    - Hassam, Childe, 1859-1935., 54 (Box 63)
      - Location Unknown, 18 (Box 63)
      - Private Collection, 6 (Box 63)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-N, 17 (Box 63)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: P-Z, 13 (Box 63)
    - Hawthorne, Charles W., 1872-1930., 5 (Box 63)
    - Heade, Martin Johnson, 1819-1904., 41 (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 5 (Box 64)
      - Miscellaneous Cities, cont., 18 (Box 64)
      - Individual Cities: Boston, 18 (Box 64)
    - Healy, George Peter Alexander, 1813- 1894., 5 (Box 64)
    - Held, Al, 1928-., 11 (Box 64)
    - Heliker, John, 1909-., 3 (Box 64)
    - Henri, Robert, 1865-1929., 12 (Box 65)
    - Henri, Robert, 1865-1929, cont., 22 (Box 65)
    - Henry, Edward Lamson, 1841-1919., 6 (Box 65)
    - Hesselius, Gustavus, 1682-1755., 8 (Box 65)
    - Hesselius, John, 1728-1778., 9 (Box 65)
    - Hicks, Edward, 1780-1849., 24 (Box 65)
    - Hirsch, Joseph, 1910-1981., 4 (Box 66)
    - Hofmann, Hans, 1880-1966., 53 (Box 66)
      - Undated, 7 (Box 66)
      - 1930-1939, 2 (Box 66)
      - 1940-1949, 13 (Box 66)
      - 1950-1959, 12 (Box 66)
      - 1960-1970, 19 (Box 66)
    - Hogue, Alexandre, 1898-., 4 (Box 66)
    - Holty, Carl Robert, 1900-1973., 4 (Box 66)
    - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910., 261 (Box 66–67)
      - Location Unknown, 20 (Box 67)
      - Private Collection, 6 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-C, 18 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: D-P, 14 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: R-Z, 10 (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: R-Z, cont., 11 (Box 67)
      - Andover, 12 (Box 68)
      - Boston, 17 (Box 68)
      - Chicago, 12 (Box 68)
      - Detroit, 12 (Box 68)
      - New Haven, 10 (Box 68)
      - New York, 22 (Box 68)
        - Individual Repositories, New York: Metropolitan Museum of Art, 22 (Box 69)
      - Philadelphia, 28 (Box 69)
      - Washington D.C., 18 (Box 69)
      - Williamstown., 29 (Box 69)
    - Hopkinson, Charles, 1869-1962., 22 (Box 69)
    - Homer, Winslow, 1836-1910., 6 (Box 69)
    - Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967., 125 (Box 70)
      - Location Unknown, 9 (Box 70)
      - Private Collection, 12 (Box 70)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 39 (Box 70)
      - New Haven, 14 (Box 71)
      - New York, 39 (Box 71)
      - Washington D.C., 12 (Box 71)
    - Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967., 2 (Box 71)
    - Hovenden, Thomas, 1840-1895., 5 (Box 71)
    - Hunt, William Morris, 1824-1879., 18 (Box 72)
    - Huntington, Daniel, 1816-1906., 9 (Box 72)
    - Hurd, Peter, 1904-1984., 6 (Box 72)
- I (Box 72)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "I" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: I., 5 (Box 72)
    - Imbert, Anthony., 1 (Box 72)
    - Ingham, Charles Cromwell., 1 (Box 72)
    - Insley, Will., 1 (Box 72)
    - Ipsen, Ernest L., 1 (Box 72)
    - Isham, Samuel., 1 (Box 72)
  - Individual Artists (Box 72)
    - Indiana, Robert, 1928-., 5 (Box 72)
    - Inman, Henry, 1801-1846., 19 (Box 72)
    - Inness, George, 1825-1894., 81 (Box 72–73)
      - Location Unknown, 10 (Box 73)
      - Private Collection, 1 (Box 73)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-L, 15 (Box 73)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: M-Z, 18 (Box 73)
      - Chicago, 18 (Box 73)
      - New York, 11 (Box 73)
      - Philadelphia, 8 (Box 73)
- J (Box 74)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "J" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ja-Joc., 25 (Box 74)
    - Jackson, Everett G., 2 (Box 74)
    - Jackson, Harry., 3 (Box 74)
    - Jacobsen, Antonio., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jacquette, Yvonne., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jarvis, Charles., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jenney, Neil., 4 (Box 74)
    - Jennings, J.S., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jensen, Bill., 2 (Box 74)
    - Jess., 2 (Box 74)
    - Jocelyn, Nathaniel., 3 (Box 74)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Joh-Ju., 22 (Box 74)
    - Johnson, Ben., 2 (Box 74)
    - Johnson, David., 2 (Box 74)
    - Johnson, Lester., 1 (Box 74)
    - Johnson, Ray., 2 (Box 74)
    - Johnston, David Claypoole., 3 (Box 74)
    - Johnston, John., 1 (Box 74)
    - Johnston, William., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jones, Fay., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jones, Nell Choate., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jouett, Matthew Harris., 1 (Box 74)
    - Judson, Alice., 1 (Box 74)
    - Jules, Mervin., 1 (Box 74)
  - Individual Artists (Box 74)
    - Jarvis, John Wesley, 1781-1840., 9 (Box 74)
    - Jenkins, Paul, 1923-., 8 (Box 74)
    - Jennys, William, act. c. 1795-1807., 9 (Box 74)
    - Jensen, Alfred, 1903-?., 5 (Box 74)
    - Johansen, John C., 1876-c. 1966., 3 (Box 75)
    - Johns, Jasper, 1930-., 42 (Box 75)
    - Johnson, Eastman, 1824-1906., 31 (Box 75)
      - Location Unknown, 1 (Box 75)
      - Private Collection, 3 (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-L, 13 (Box 75)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: M-Z, 14 (Box 75)
    - Johnson, Lester, 1919-., 5 (Box 76)
    - Johnson, William H., 1901-1970., 5 (Box 76)
    - Johnston, Henrietta, c. 1670-1728., 8 (Box 76)
    - Johnston, Joshua, act. 1796-1824., 7 (Box 76)
    - Jones, Joe, 1909-1963., 5 (Box 76)
- K (Box 76)
  Includes a folder of miscellaneous clippings for various "K" artists.
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ka., 11 (Box 76)
    - Kabak, Robert., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kahn, Wolf., 2 (Box 76)
    - Kaldis, Aristodemos., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kanowitz, Howard., 2 (Box 76)
    - Kaprow, Allan., 1 (Box 76)
    - Katz, Paul., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kauffer, E. McKnight., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kauffman, Craig., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kaye, Otis., 1 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ke., 9 (Box 76)
    - Kemble, E.W., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kemmelmeyer, Frederick., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kent, Donald., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kepes, Gyorgy., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kepets, Hugh., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kerkam, Earl., 2 (Box 76)
    - Kern, Richard., 2 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Ki., 6 (Box 76)
    - Kienbusch, William., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kiesler, Frederick., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kim, Byron., 1 (Box 76)
    - King, Samuel., 3 (Box 76)
  - Miscellaneous Artists: Kl-Ku., 18 (Box 76)
    - Klarwein, Mati., 1 (Box 76)
    - Klitgaard, Georgina., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kloss, Gene., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kohlmeyer, Ida., 1 (Box 76)
    - Komar and Melamid., 2 (Box 76)
    - Koons, Jeff., 1 (Box 76)
    - Korman, Harriet., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kosuth, Joseph., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kozloff, Joyce., 1 (Box 76)
    - Krause, Herman., 1 (Box 76)
    - Kuehne, Max., 3 (Box 76)
    - Kulicke, Robert., 1 (Box 76)
  - Individual Artists (Box 77)
    - Kane, John, 1860-1934., 5 (Box 77)
    - Kantor, Morris, 1896-1974., 6 (Box 77)
    - Karfiol, Bernard, 1886-1952., 10 (Box 77)
    - Katz, Alex, 1927-., 12 (Box 77)
    - Keller, Deane, 1901-., 6 (Box 77)
    - Keller, Henry George, 1869-1949., 4 (Box 77)
    - Kelly, Ellsworth, 1923-., 21 (Box 77)
    - Kensett, John Frederick, 1816-1872., 24 (Box 78)
      - Miscellaneous Cities: A-Z, 17 (Box 78)
      - New York, 7 (Box 78)
    - Kent, Rockwell, 1882-1971., 22 (Box 78)
    - King, Charles Bird, 1785-1862., 6 (Box 79)